Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1937-1995, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-44, OV 81-83; 43.6 linear feet)
  - Musée d'Art Moderne de la Ville de Paris, 1983-1984, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Musée d'Art Moderne de la Ville de Paris, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Musée de l'Athéenée, 1971, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Musée des Augustins, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Musée Cantini, 1964, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Musée Fernand Léger, 1957-1962, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Musée du Louvre, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Musée de l'Orangerie, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Musée d'Orsay, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Musées des Beaux-Arts de Montréal, 1990, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Musées de Bordeaux, 1966-1972 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Museo de Arte Contempraneo, Barcelona, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Museo de Arte Contempraneo, Caracas, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Museo de Arte Moderno, Mexico, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Museo Mural Diego Rivera, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Museo Nacional Centro de Arte Reina Sofia, 1987-1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Museo Progressivo d'Arte Contemporanea, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Museu de Arte Moderna, Sao Paolo, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Museu de Ceà, Barcelona, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Museu Picasso, Barcelona, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - The Museum for African Art, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - The Museum for African Art, 1983-1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design, 1944-1958, 1965-1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Museum Boymans-van Beuningen, 1964, 1969-1971, 1976-1977, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1941-1944, 1961-1966, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1964-1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1954-1963 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Museum Ludwig, 1978-1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1990-1995 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1961-1964 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1951-1954 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1946-1950 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1943-1945 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1938-1942 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - The Museum of Modern Art Gallery of Washington, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Museum Am Ostwall, Dortmund, 1962-1966 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Museum West, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Myers, Mrs. Louis S. (Mary), 1966-1969, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous M, circa 1937-1995, (5 folders) (Box 28, Folder 42-46)
  - Miscellaneous M, circa 1937-1995, (23 folders); (see also OV 82) (Box 29, Folder 1-23)
  - N. W. Ayer and Son, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Nahmad, Giuseppe, 1990, (see also Davlyn Gallery; Galleria Internazionale) (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Nagoya City Art Museum, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Nagoya Gallery, 1985-1994 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Namuth, Hans, 1960-1962, 1979-1981, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - La Napoule Art Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Nash, Judith Small, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1981-1983, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Nathanson, Irwin S., 1940-1946 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - National Academy of Design, 1944-1948 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - National Council for U. S. Art, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1975, (see also OV 81; OV 83) (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1946, 1951, 1967-1974 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - National Gallery of Victoria, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - National Museum of African Art, 1981-1988 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - The National Museum of Ceramic Art, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - The National Museum of Modern Art, Tokyo, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - The National Museum of Modern Art, Tokyo, 1976-1977, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - The National Museum of Woman in the Arts, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - The National Portrait Gallery, 1980, 1987-1992 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Nebelung, Hella, 1953-1954, 1963, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Neidlinger, Charles, 1951-1962 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Paul, 1959-1963 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Netter, Anne, 1948-1952, 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Neuberger, Roy R., 1942-1945, 1959-1969, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Neumann, Hans, 1965-1975, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Neumann, Hans, 1955-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Neumann, Morton G., 1948-1959, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Neumann, Vera, 1966-1973, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey State Museum, 1946-1947, 1967, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - New Orleans Museum of Art, 1978, 1992, (see also Isaac Delgado Museum of Art) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The New York Psychoanalytic Institute, 1944, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The New York Public Library, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - New York Studio School, 1968-1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - The New York Times, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - New York University, 1974-1990 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - New York Wellesley Club, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - The New Yorker, 1965, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - The Newark Museum, 1945, 1955-1957, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Newberry, John S., Jr., 1943-1951 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Newman, Albert H., 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Newsweek Magazine, 1969-1984 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Nichi-Futsu Gallery, 1953-1957 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Niveau Gallery, 1943-1955, 1961, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1943-1948 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1968-1971, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1967-1969, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Norton Gallery and School of Art, 1947-1967, 1979-1983 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Norton Simon, Inc., 1969-1974, 1983-1984, (see also Simon, Norton; Norton Simon Museum of Art; Hunt Foods & Industries Museum of Art) (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Norton Simon Museum of Art, 1976-1986, (see also Simon, Norton; Norton Simon, Inc.; Hunt Foods & Industries Museum of Art) (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Nygaard, Kaare K., 1970-1977, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous N, circa 1937-1995, (12 folders) (Box 30, Folder 32-43)
  - The Oakland Museum, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Obelisk Gallery, 1957-1963, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - O'Connor, Mrs. Liam (Elizabeth), 1975-1980 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Odets, Clifford, 1946-1948 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Oehlschlaeger, Frank J., 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Oehlschlaeger, Frank J., 1945-1955 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - O'Hana Gallery, 1951-1956, 1963-1966, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Oklahoma Art Gallery, 1974-1982 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Openair Museum for Sculpture, Middelheim, 1960-1962, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Oppenheim, Neil, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Osborn, Robert and Elodie, 1974-1987 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Osborn, Robert and Elodie, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Osborn, Robert and Elodie, 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Osborn, Robert and Elodie, 1939, 1960-1966 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - österreichisches Museum für Angewandte Kunst, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Outlines Gallery, 1942-1947 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous O, circa 1937-1995, (7 folders); (see also OV 83) (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
  - The Pace Gallery, 1976-1981, 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Packard, Martin and Enid, 1969, 1986-1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Paddock, Dennis E., 1961-1970 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Paget, Dennis, 1977-1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Paget, Gerald C., 1946-1951 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Paideia Trading Co., Ltd., 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Paine, Stephen D., 1961-1966, 1973-1977, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Palais des Beaux Arts, Brussels, 1971, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Palais des Beaux Arts, Charleroi, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Palevsky, Max, 1967-1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Paley, William S. and Dorothy, 1938-1950 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Palley, Reese, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Palmer, Herbert B., 1964-1969 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Pan American Union, 1944-1951, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Panicali Fine Art, 1982-1989 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Pantheon Books, Inc., 1942, 1947, 1955-1958 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1949-1954, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1947-1848 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Park Synagogue Art Festival, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1966-1973 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1959-1965 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1953-1955 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1948-1950 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1940-1947 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Paul Rosenberg & Co., 1939-1944, 1953, 1958-1967, 1973, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Pearl, Leonard P., 1964-1970 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Pease, Perry R. and Mary, 1942-1961, 1967-1974, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Peck, Gregory, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Peck, Sam, 1949, 1960-1961, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Peel, Edmund, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Peet, Herbert O., 1950-1952 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Pei, I. M., 1957, 1966, 1978, 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Penguin Books Ltd., 1965-1966, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Penker, Theo. M., III, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Penney, Charles R., 1966-1978 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - The Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1950-1968 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - The Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1963-1965 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Penson & Company, Inc., 1938-1948, 1961-1970 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Pepczynski, Al, 1947-1950 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - PepsiCo., 1971-1981 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Pepsi-Cola's Annual Art Competition, 1946-1948 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Pereny, Madeline, 1942-1945, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Perin, Bradford, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Perls, Joseph Nicholas, 1942, 1965-1980 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Perry, Norman, 1945-1949 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Peters, Ernest S., 1943-1949, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Peterson, Joan, 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Petrides, Paul, 1963-1975, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Petrides, Paul, 1937-1940, 1949-1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Petter, Henry, 1942, 1957, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Pfannstiel, Arthur S., 1960, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Phaidon Press Limited, 1979-1982, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1944-1948 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia College of Art, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1963-1974, 1981-1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1938-1951, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Philbrook Art Center, 1944-1946, 1951-1956, 1967, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Phillips, Anne W., 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - The Phillips Collection, 1965-1967, 1978-1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Phillips, Duncan, 1938-1944, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Phillips, Louis, 1952-1956 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1941-1948 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Phillips, Neill, 1950-1964 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Phoenix Art Museum, 1958-1970 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Picasso, Claude, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1950-1951, 1959, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Pick, Grant J., 1949-1961 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Pictures Publishing Company, 1944-1952 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Pierre Matisse Gallery, 1937-1945, 1957-1962, 1974-1978 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Pincus, Irwin Nat, 1952-1959 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Pleasanton, Faith, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Pollock, Helen Channing, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Pope, Gustavus D., 1960-1963 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1973-1977 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1957, 1970-1972, (see also OV 83) (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Porter, Cole, 1941-1944 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Porter, David, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Portland Art Museum, 1938-1939, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Poston, George, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Potter, Mrs. A. Cuthbert (Bernice S.), 1953-1956 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Powell, Watson, Jr., 1966-1972 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Powers, John G., 1969-1971, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Préjger, Lionel, 1973-1989 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Price, Vincent, 1942-1948 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Price, Vincent Barrett, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Price, Winston H., 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1951-1959, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Priebe, Karl, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Princeton Gallery of Fine Art, 1985-1989 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Princeton University, 1966-1971 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Providence Art Club, 1960-1965 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Public Education Association, 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Public Education Association, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Public Education Association, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1940-1942, 1949, 1955-1956, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - The Purnell Galleries, 1949-1952 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Pyrch & Co. Ltd., 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous P, circa 1937-1995, (8 folders) (Box 32, Folder 58-65)
  - Miscellaneous P, circa 1937-1995, (14 folders) (Box 33, Folder 1-14)
  - Quatre Chemins - Editart, 1956, 1963-1972, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Quatrochi, Paul D., 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Queens College, 1957-1958, 1967, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - The Queens Museum, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Quinby, Elise Howland, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Quintana's Fine Art, 1986-1990 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Q, circa 1937-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - R. Kraus Hardware, Inc., 1956-1971 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - R. L. Polk & Co., Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Racolin, Alexander E., 1956-1959, 1970, 1977, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Randall, Robert N., 1968-1979 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Randall, Tony, 1959, 1968-1969, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Random House, Inc., 1966-1972, 1980-1987 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Ransohoff, J. Louis and Jane K., 1940-1944, 1962-1967 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Rapaport, Benjamin, 1947-1949 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Rash, Dillman A., 1958, 1971-1978, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Ravinia Festival Association, 1961-1965 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Raykis, Vladimir, 1939-1946 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - The Reader's Digest, 1944-1947, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Redefer, Rederick L. and Helen S., 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Regency Worldwide Packing, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Reichenbach, François, 1951-1956 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Reichenbach, Philippe, 1960-1963; 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Reicher, Harry J., 1953, 1962, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Reichman, Fred, 1972-1977, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Reinhold, Arthur E., 1971-1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Reisman, Marshall M., 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Remis, Robert E., 1967, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Renaud, L. B., 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Renofab Process Corporation, 1957-1981 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Renou et Poyet, 1973, 1984-1992 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Resor, Mr. and Mrs. Stanley and Miss Helen, 1941-1944, 1954, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Ret, Etienne, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Rewald, John, 1940-1941, 1946, 1964-1975 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Rewald, Walter, Reni, and Miriam, 1940-1942, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Riccio, John, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Rice, Frederick, 1941-1943, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Richard Berk Gallery, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Richard Feigen Gallery, 1969-1978, 1985-1991 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Richard Feigen Gallery, 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Richard Gray Gallery, 1965-1975, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Richards, Ann Kendall, 196-1980 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Richards, Arnold D., 1970-1976, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Richardson, John, 1955-1959, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Richmond, Frederick W., 1952-1964 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Richter, Horace, 1958, 1963-1966, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Ridder, Bernard H. and Jane Delano, 1963, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Rigosi, Claudio, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Rineberg, Stephen R., 1969-1980, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Rivas, Helen W., 1952-1964 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Robbins, Ruth S., 1977-1978, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Robert C. Vose Galleries, 1944, 1951-1953 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Robert Hounigringer, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Robert Hounigringer, Inc., 1961-1968 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Roberts, Russell, 1947-1952 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Robinson, Edward G., 1938-1944 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Rock, Arthur, 1967-1971 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1950, 1958-1960, 1965-1968, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1953-1978 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - The Rockefeller University, 1970-1987 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Rodgers, Richard and Dorothy, 1963-1970, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Rodman, Selden, 1944-1949, 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Roland, Browse & Delbanco, 1959-1963, 1968-1974 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Rollings, H. Kelley, 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Rollins College, 1940, 1951, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Roman Bronze Works, Inc., 1981-1982, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Rome, Morton E., 1953-1958 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Roméro, Marcos, 1955, 1960-1967 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Rose, Billy, 1943-1944, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Roseman, Charles E., Jr., 1943-1947 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Rosenberg, Jacob, 1945-1952 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Rosenman, Colin, Kaye, Petschek, Freund, & Emil, 1975-1983 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Rosenwald, James B., Jr., 1957-1960, 1969-1978 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Rosenwald, Julius II and Judy, 1941, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Roth, H. E. and June L., 1967-1977 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Roth, Marvin and Ronnie, 1969-1978 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Rothschild, Herbert, 1940, 1951-1957, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Rouault, Isabelle, 1950, 1956-1966, 1977-1987 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Royal Academy of Arts, 1985-1993 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Rubel, Edward and Earline, 1970-1981, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Rübel, Peter A., 1963-1984 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Rübel, Peter A., 1955-1962 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Rübel, Peter A., 1948-1954 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Ruder & Finn Incorporated, 1961-1970 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Ruff, Curtis C. and Roberta D., 1968-1969, 1979, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Rugoff, Donald S., 1968-1970, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Rusche, Werner, 1951-1958 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Rutgers University, 1958, 1978-1982, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Rutland Gallery, 1964-1974 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Ruvolo, Felix, 1943-1947 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous R, circa 1937-1995, (8 folders) (Box 34, Folder 74-81)
  - Miscellaneous R, circa 1937-1995, (18 folders) (Box 35, Folder 1-18)
  - Saalfield, Albrecht and Agnes, 1967-1973, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Saarinen, Aline, 1955-1956, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Sabet, Claude, 1969-1973 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Sabet, Gabriel, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Sackler, Arthur M., 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Saidenberg, Daniel and Eleanore, 1944-1981, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - The St. Louis Art Museum, 1979, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - The Saint Louis Ambassadors, Inc., 1978 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - The Saint Paul Gallery and School of Art, 1938-1944 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - The Salvador Dalí Archives, 1972-1984 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - The Salvador Dalí Museum, 1976-1991 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Sampliner, Paul H., 1962-1975 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Sampson, Harold, 1976-1981 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - The San Antonio Art League, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - San Diego Museum of Art, 1968-1975, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1960-1975, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1953-1956 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1939-1944 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Sandler, Ted, 1948-1956 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - The Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1959-1968, 1973-1975, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Sarlie, Jacques, 1948-1961 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Sarnoff, Mrs. Stanley J. (Charlotte), 1949-1952, 1968, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Schaefer-Simmern, Henry, 1952-1957 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Schaeffer Galleries, Inc., 1938-1939, 1945-1949 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Schaffer, Diane, 1963-1976 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Schames, Samson, 1950-1955 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Schary, Doré, 1941-1943 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Schary, Saul, 1940-1944 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Scheffield, Charles, 1969-1972 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Scheuber, Sylvia Fein, 1945-1949, 1956-1958 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Scheuber, Sylvia Fein, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Scheuber, Sylvia Fein, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Schick, Georges, 1960-1967 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Schick, Georges, 1956-1959 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Schick, Georges, 1954-1955 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Schick, Georges, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Schick, Georges, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Schick, Georges, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Schick, Georges, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Schick, Georges, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Schick, Georges, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Schick, Georges, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Schick, Georges, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Schick, Georges, 1939-1945 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Schindler, Gustave, 1963-1966, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)